omgmachines.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Policy – OMG Machines

**PRIVACY POLICY  **

**Last Updated on September 13, 2018**

**OMG Machines is committed to respecting your privacy.  **

OMG Machines Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from http://lizherrera.com (the “Site”).

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

    – “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

    – “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

    – “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers [[INSERT ANY OTHER PAYMENT TYPES ACCEPTED]]), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

Communicate with you;

Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and

When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store–you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

Behavioral ADVERTISING

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

    FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads

    GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous

    BING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.

DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

YOUR RIGHTS

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

DATA RETENTION

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

MINORS

The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18.

CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at liz@lizherrera.com or by mail using the details provided below:

  1444 Biscayne Blvd Suite 206, Miami, FL, 33132, United States

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**BUSINESS INFORMATION**

Information that is collected by webinar coordinators or moderators is considered confidential. We will not view Business Information except as necessary to appropriately support the service or as required by law. (Business Information includes schedules, attendee lists, subject names, email addresses, names, session records, and any other business information used while in session) When an attendee registers with one of our customers for an online meeting, webinar or training, that information is provided to the organizer of the session. OMG Machines,  may store that information to fulfill our obligation to our customers, but we will not use the information to send marketing communications for OMG Machines,  services or third party offers to attendees. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit while in session and utilizing the chat feature can be read, collected or used by the meeting organizer and other meeting participants. Chat logs and meeting recordings are not stored or viewable by OMG Machines,  and are only available locally to meeting coordinators and moderators. We will not view business information, except as necessary to appropriately support the service and for the purpose of anticipating, diagnosing, supporting or resolving any problems that might limit or disrupt the quality of our customers’ service experience or as required by law.

**PARTNERS**

In some cases we provide services or sell product lines jointly with other businesses. For these co-branded offerings in which a third party is involved in your transactions, we will sometimes share or jointly collect customer information related to those transactions with that third party. On the co-branded registration pages we will state who is collecting or receiving the information and whose privacy statement governs its use so that you will know at the time you create your account exactly how your information will be used. If you are registered with OMG Machines,  through a partnership and you request to opt out of receiving promotional updates, in order to comply with the provisions in the Can Spam Act, we will also provide your email address to that partner so that they may also discontinue sending you messages on behalf of OMG Machines,  .

**AFFILIATES**

We may sometimes share or jointly collect information with our parent entity and the wholly owned subsidiaries and affiliated divisions of our parent company entity. Sharing this information helps us make your customer experience more seamless and efficient by allowing us to improve our marketing efforts to better target customer needs, streamline our processes and consolidate our backend business systems.

**SESSION RECORDS**

To maintain our quality of service and to assist in the analysis of product performance, we may also gather data on connection information, including the timing and size of all packets sent over the Internet during a session. The gathered information is used only to ensure the highest quality experience possible when using OMG Machines,  products.

**SECURITY INFORMATION**

OMG Machines,  also collects certain standard information about your computer for security and identification purposes. This information may include: IP addresses, domain names, access times, cookies and other unique identifying information of machines that have our software downloaded and installed on them. This information is used for the operation of the service, to identify and protect our customers and to control unauthorized use or abuse of our services. All information is encrypted during transmission and is stored securely within our servers.

**SURVEYS**

In addition to required member information, we may conduct surveys and ask users to volunteer demographic information to be used on an aggregate basis for internal market research, presentation to advertisers and joint research projects with outside companies involved in product development. We use such information to better focus our product and personalize the scope of services offered to each individual user.

**SOCIAL MEDIA**

 Our Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. These services will also authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. These Services may give you the option to post information about your activities on our websites to your profile page to share with others within your network. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

**TESTIMONIALS**

With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us via one of the methods listed in this Online Privacy Policy.

**ANALYTICS**

We continuously improve our websites and our products and we utilize different third party web analytics tools to help us do so. We are interested in how visitors use our websites, our desktop tools, our mobile applications, what they like and dislike, and where they have problems. Our products, desktop tools and mobile applications use analytical tools to understand feature usage patterns, to enhance and improve your product experience and offer you specific usage tips and guidance. In connection with normal business operations, as well as to increase functionality and enhance your user experience, this usage information may be linked to personal information that we have about individual users. We maintain ownership of this data and we do not share this type of data about individual users with third parties.

Our mobile applications will also use analytical tools to help gather non-personally identifiable data about download and application usage. In our use of mobile applications we may utilize GeoLocation data but only if you specifically opt-in to collection of such data in connection with a particular service. We may use information such as IP addresses to determine the general geographic locations areas of our visitors, but this information is not correlated to personal information about individual users. The web beacons used in conjunction with these tools may gather data such as what browser a person uses, what operating systems are used, domain names, MIME types, what is downloaded, and what content, products and services are reviewed when visiting or registering for services at one of our websites or using one of our mobile applications.

This information is used solely to assist OMG Machines,  in maintaining a more effective and useful websites and products for our customers. This data will not be shared with third parties without your prior consent or unless required by law.

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. We use cookies to track user traffic patterns and hold certain registration information. When you register at OMG Machines,  sites, we use cookies to store unique, randomly assigned user IDs that we generate for administrative purposes. These cookies enable you to enter the OMG Machines,  sites without having to log on each time. We do not store passwords or any Personal Information about you in the cookies.

Local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, may be used by third parties for some of our product training videos. These cookies are used to store preferences for the videos such as volume control. Flash cookies are not used to back-up, recreate or re-spawn a browser cookie that a user may delete. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and way data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies please click here.

**3\. With whom does OMG Machines,   share the information?**

Ensuring your privacy is important to us. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties.

OMG Machines,  products and services by necessity require us to provide some of your information to third parties. We may occasionally employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments, sending postal mail and email, analyzing data and providing marketing assistance. They have access to personal information needed only to perform their functions and may not use it for any other purpose. Further, they must process the personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Also, in the event that OMG Machines,  or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets. For more information on how you will be notified in this instance, see Section 5 below.

Occasionally we send offers to select groups of OMG Machines,  customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not share your personal information with the other businesses. Except in the limited instances as stated above, we will never voluntarily share personally identifiable information with any third party without the user’s express consent or unless compelled by applicable state and federal laws. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

OMG Machines,  does not control the practices of our affiliates. If you have questions about how affiliates use the information gathered when you link to them, please read their privacy policies.

Links to other sites: This website may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by OMG Machines,  . Please be aware that we, OMG Machines,  , are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

**4\. How can I review, correct and update my personal information?**

If you wish to change or review your personal information, go to your My Profile page. There you can access or update the personal information and account history we have on file. Please contact us at omg@omgmachines.com if you need assistance in updating or reviewing your information. OMG Machines,  will respond to your request to review the information we have on file for you within 30 days.

**5\. How can I opt out of OMG Machines, ’s collection, use and distribution of my information?**

To change your email subscription status to receive or to stop receiving marketing communications or third-party promotions administered by OMG Machines,  or to opt out of OMG Machines, ’s collection, use and distribution of your information as stated above, please go to the Unsubscribe page, enter your email address and then click Submit. Users who would like to deactivate their account can contact us at omg@omgmachines.com for assistance.

This privacy policy is subject to change. If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via email prior to the changes taking effect. If OMG Machines,  or any of its assets are acquired by another company we will notify you via email about this transaction and the transfer of your personal information. You will have a choice as to whether or not you consent to the usage of your information in a different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our website notifying users of the change.

**6\. How does OMG Machines,   protect my information from loss, misuse or alteration?**

OMG Machines,  uses industry-standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of personally identifiable information, including encryption, firewalls and SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). Nevertheless, we remind you that no security measure is perfect.

OMG Machines,  is not liable for loss of passwords due to user carelessness. If you lose control over your password, you may lose control over your personally identifiable information. If you believe your password has been compromised, we recommend that you immediately change your password. For information on how to do this, please see email our support chat at: support@I Build Your Brand.com

**7\. Who can I ask if I have additional questions?**

For additional inquiries about the privacy of your information,

you can contact OMG Machines,  by emailing us at

omg@omgmachines.com.

**OMG Machines – COPYRIGHT 2018 – ALL RIGHTS RESERVED**

*Earnings and income representations made by , OMG Machines and their advertisers/sponsors are aspirational statements only of your earnings potential. These results are not typical and results will vary.
